you know what it has been a tough week
there's a lot of anger and shouting
recently some of it within the the last
30 seconds to be honest so I felt that
this would be a great time for a segment
that highlights some feel-good stories
about the real people out in real
America it's a brilliant idea that I
just had and small town stations have
been stealing from me for years take a
look at some of the week's best videos
in our segment called hey watch this to
get to meet some more of Eric's heroes
it's time for cool people doing cool
things seven everyday heroes for
goodness sake I'm Bill Anderson oh for
goodness sake I'm Jordan Klepper and
unlike local news I can afford lamp
chase you know what let's take the focus
off of me and put it on the everyman
doing good and my long-running
first-time segment Jordans heroes
first up a man who loves the great
outdoors almost as much as he loves
helping those in need which is a lot if
that wasn't clear
a man is travelling across the country
to spread goodwill and his only tool is
a lawn mower Ronnie Smith Jr's known as
lawn mower man he says the idea came
from a chance encounter he had one day
with an elderly man like he was
struggling so I pulled over and helped
them out that night I decided to move
three lawns for the elderly disabled
single mothers and veterans Smith says
he'll travel to all 50 states and mow
lawns for those in need
Wow inspiring story mowing lawns for the
needy in all 50 states your neighbors
must love you
heck the whole country is gonna be your
neighbors soon everyone's friend that's
you Rodney
everybody loves Rodney Rodney must feel
pretty good about yourself pretty good
hey Rodney you think you're better than
me is that what you think Rodney I can
mow lawns in all 50 states I'm handy I'm
good with tools
I built a birdhouse in fifth grade a
good one the birds still in it I can buy
a lawn mower
I can definitely buy one and find one
and identify one in a hardware store
that I could buy it in a heartbeat how
much could it be I don't know
thirty thousand dollars sip probably
could be plus I can go to any state I
want as long as it's not both Dakota's
or one of the Virginia's they know what
they did
screw you Rodney you're not better than
me this next story is sure to make you
smile and maybe also a bit hungry a
fast-food worker in Chesterfield County
is receiving a lot of praise after this
video went viral you can see him run
Forrest run chasing down a customer who
forgot part of our order the dedicated
workers successfully got the customer's
second bag of food to her before jogging
back and looking just a little bit tired
oh well you can't argue with that that's
just a nice thing to do
glad a nice guy like that in the middle
of the country is getting that kind of
attention he's probably feeling pretty
good about you think you're better than
me that's not a run that's a shuffle at
best
I've sprinted out of chick-fil-a's twice
as fast as that carrying way more bags
of moral
dubious fried chicken and how dare you
abandon your post it's chaos back at
that chick-fil-a with you gone they're
serving burritos and grilling pad thai
and not weighing in on what constitutes
love anymore you're a bot sir how on
earth can you think you're better than
me
up next have you got a heart ticket in
your chest careful
this story is sure to melt it super
daddy saved the big show take a look
little Bella hysterical crying on stage
during her annual ballet recital
dad appears from the wings try to calm
her down with the baby Wow holding a
baby yeah she joined the ballet line I
got this I'm super dad you super dad
you're better than me
you think you're such a great dad
because you're amazing moment of super
dad 'no swin my role and your kids will
love you forever and ever you think I
can't go viral
you think I can't dance with a baby
someone give me a baby yes there we go
give me some music some real super
ballet dad ah yeah see you are not
better than me shove this up your
facebook be you know what puppy me
it
oh did you have a dog yeah
who's your super dad now as a
matter of fact bring on the summer
interns uh yeah see this is easy I could
do this all day
dance with me kids dance with me dance
with me my kids love me too
no one's better than me I'm the super
dad opposers are there any three words
more exciting than click and subscribe
yes Hillary shot Lincoln subscribe now
and find out the truth they don't want
you to know and by day I mean losers
looking for YouTube handouts without
clicking subscribe do it